Vedika Parvez, Product Manager

Chennai, India, +91 81440 25596, me@vedikaparvez.com

PROFILE

Hey there! I'm Vedika, your go-to gal for all things B2B SaaS product management with a background in linguistic AI research. Over the last 6 years, I've journeyed through the tech world, leading the charge from ideation to execution, it's been quite the ride!

What drives me? It's the thrill in mastering 'systems thinking' allowing me to approach product management with a holistic vision, the joy of seeing a product come to life, and the satisfaction of knowing it makes a difference.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Jun 2022 — Present

Product Manager, Rocketlane

Chennai

- Latest Launch: Customer Portal 2.0 (https://lnkd.in/gAAc8XkF) Reimagined the customer portal
 from the ground up, transforming it into a sleek, customizable, website-like experience. This redesign drove
 over 50% boost in user engagement, secured enterprise deals, and increased end-user adoption, enabling
 effortless collaboration throughout the pre and post-sales journey.
- Leading the Rocketlane Marketplace Vision A centralized marketplace to deliver seamless integrations and a developer-first experience, enabling custom workflows and powerful enterprise integrations. This feature empowers vendors and customers to extend the platform's functionality, supporting complex workflows for professional services teams and addressing unique business needs across industries.
- Currently building AI-Sheets, an enterprise feature aimed at simplifying data management and improving
 collaboration between cross-functional teams, ensuring seamless project tracking and more efficient
 implementation workflows.
- Led the end-to-end implementation of the Automations feature Built the automation engine from
 the ground up, driving a 75% adoption customer-wide. This feature significantly increases operational
 efficiency, saving team members valuable time for high-impact tasks, while unlocking critical governance
 workflows that enhance Rocketlane's overall functionality and performance.

www.rocketlane.com

Jan 2021 — Apr 2023

Founder, AdEase

Chennai

- Ideated the AdEase platform from inception to production.
- Managed a team of designers and developers to build the product. Formulate and incorporated the business strategy into product strategy.
- Executed product strategy by developing proprietary creative generation algorithms using image processing and computer vision models.
- Collaborated closely with designers and ML enthusiasts to develop proprietary creative generation
 algorithms using image processing and computer vision models. This effort resulted in creation of ad
 creatives faster than a human graphic designer.
- Managed all aspects of in-life products, including customer feedback, requirements, and issues.

www.adease.ai

Apr 2020 - Nov 2020

Data Scientist, SmartTerra

Bengaluru

- · Worked as a data scientist at Smartterra, an AI-powered operational intelligence platform for water utilities.
- Developed time series prediction models with Long-Short Term Memory (LSTM)-Recurrent Neural Network (RNN) to predict water consumption behavior of residents of Bengaluru City.
- Developed and optimized Imbalanced Classifier models with Support Vector Machine (SVM) and Local Outlier Factor (LOF) to detect anomalous metering.

www.smartterra.io

Jan 2018 — Apr 2020

Research Associate, Gemini Associates

Chennai

- Key member of ARA's Cognitive Computing and Computational Linguistics team, driving behavior change through an end-to-end messaging system.
- Collaborated on an empirical study with the principal investigator, shaping the P3
 (Personalized-Persuasive-Pragmatic) Messaging Approach to optimize digital messages.
- Designed the linguistic framework for generating 20 cognitive message frames, enabling tailored, impactful
 communication.

EDUCATION

Jul 2014 — Jun 2018

Bachelors in Engineering, SRM University

Chennai